<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright (c) Lester J. Clark and Contributors. -->
<!-- Licensed under the MIT License. -->
<!-- LJCBackupProfile.xml -->
<members>
  <!-- Assembly -->
  <LJCBackupCommonLib5>
    <summary>
      Contains common backup code.
    </summary>
  </LJCBackupCommonLib5>

  <!-- Class -->
  <LJCBackupProfile>
    <summary>
      Represents a backup profile.
    </summary>
  </LJCBackupProfile>

  <!-- Constructor Methods -->
  <Constructor>
    <summary>
      Initializes an object instance.
    </summary>
  </Constructor>
  <ConstructorParams>
    <summary>
      Initializes an object instance with the supplied values.
    </summary>
    <param name="name">The backup profile name.</param>
  </ConstructorParams>

  <!-- Properties -->
  <ChangesFilespec>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the changes file name.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        This is the name of a file that contains the backup "copy" and "delete"
        commands.<br />
        These commands can be viewed and edited before running the
        code to apply these changes.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </ChangesFilespec>
  <IncludeFilters>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the included file filters.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        A list of file patterns using wild cards separated with the
        "Vertical Bar" (pipe) character. For example: "*.cs|*.sln|*.csproj
        |*.cmd"
      </para>
      <para>
        Files that match one of these file patterns will be included in the
        Code Backup.
      </para>
      <para>
        Files will be copied to the target folder if they do not exist there
        or the source file has changed.
      </para>
      <para>
        Files will be deleted from the target folder if they do not exist in the
        source folder. This keeps the folders synched.<br />
        However, this behavior must be managed carefully to prevent losing code.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </IncludeFilters>
  <IncludeMissingTargetFolders>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the include missing target folders flag.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        The standard behavior is to only copy files where the target folder
        already exists.
      </para>
      <para>
        The standard behavior uses this implicit way of controlling which
        folders get backed up instead of having to explicitly list the source
        folders to be included.
      </para>
      <para>
        When a new source folder is created, it must be copied to or created in
        the target codeline to be included in the backup.
      </para>
      <para>
        Setting the IncludeMissingTargetFolders property to true overrides the
        standard behavior and will create missing target folders.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </IncludeMissingTargetFolders>
  <Name>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the profile name.
    </summary>
  </Name>
  <SkipFiles>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the skip file list.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        A list of file patterns using wild cards separated with the
        "Vertical Bar" (pipe) character. For example: "Build*.cmd|Example*.cs"
      </para>
      <para>
        Files that match one of these file patterns will not be included in the
        Code Backup.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </SkipFiles>
  <SkipFoldersFilespec>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the skipped folder file name.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        This is the name of a file that contains partial target folder paths
        for folders that are intentionally excluded.
      </para>
      <para>
        The backup program writes a partial target folder path to the file
        "MissingFolders.txt" when the backup detects a missing target folder.
        <br />
        This is notification of a source folder that is not included in the
        backup.
      </para>
      <para>
        Adding a partial folder to the SkipFolders file prevents getting a
        missing folders entry for a source folder you intended to exclude.<br />
        This makes it easier to see the folders you did not intend to exclude.
      </para>      
    </remarks>
  </SkipFoldersFilespec>
  <SourceCodeline>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the source codeline value.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        The source codeline is the name of the source folder that holds the code
        specific to that codeline.
      </para>
      <para>
        A codeline contains the solutions, projects and other code that is
        a version of a framework, product or other associated code.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </SourceCodeline>
  <SourceRoot>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the source root value.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        The source root is the full path to the source folder that contains the
        source codeline folders.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </SourceRoot>
  <TargetCodeline>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the target codeline value.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        The target codeline is the name of the target folder that holds the code
        specific to that codeline.
      </para>
      <para>
        A codeline contains the solutions, projects and other code that is
        a version of a framework, product or other associated code.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </TargetCodeline>
  <TargetRoot>
    <summary>
      Gets or sets the target root value.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        The target root is the full path to the target folder that contains the
        target codeline folders.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </TargetRoot>
  <SourcePath>
    <summary>
      Gets the full source path.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      The SourcePath is the full path combination of the SourceRoot and
      SourceCodeline.
    </remarks>
  </SourcePath>
  <TargetPath>
    <summary>
      Gets the full target path.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      The TargetPath is the full path combination of the TargetRoot and
      TargetCodeline.
    </remarks>
  </TargetPath>
</members>