<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright (c) Lester J. Clark and Contributors. -->
<!-- Licensed under the MIT License. -->
<!-- LJCBackupProgram.xml -->
<members>
  <!-- Assembly -->
  <LJCBackup5>
    <summary>
      Contains classes for code backup.
    </summary>
  </LJCBackup5>

  <!-- Class -->
  <LJCBackupProgram>
    <summary>
      A Code Backup program.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>
        The program entry class.
      </para>
      <para>
        The backup program contains several steps. These are described here at a
        high level.
      </para>
      <para>
        First the program creates a "Changes" file. This contains "Copy" commands
        with the names of the files that will be copied to the backup target. These
        are files that were added or changed in the backup source by the developer.
      </para>
      <para>
        It also contains "Delete" commands with the names of the files that will be
        deleted from the backup target. These are files that are still in the backup
        target but have been delete in the backup source by the developer.
      </para>
      <para>
        The developer can modify the "Changes" file before the next step. This
        may include actions such as removing deletes that the developer wants to
        verify before the actual backup is performed.
      </para>
      <para>
        The backup program then reads and applies the change commands contained in
        the "Changes" file.
      </para>
      <para>
        Note:
        The LJC Code Backup program does not contain code "Merge" functionality. A
        code "Merge" may be performed manually by the developer before promoting
        code to the version control codeline.
      </para>
      <para>-- Assembly Level Remarks </para>
      <para>
        The Code Backup program is part of the
        <span class="commonType">LJCBackup5</span>
        solution.
      </para>
      <para>Referenced Assemblies</para>
      <para>
        &lt;div class='Text'&gt;LJCBackupChangesLib5&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class='Text'&gt;LJCBackupCommonLib5&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class='Text'&gt;LJCCreateFileChangesLib5&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;div class='Text'&gt;LJCNetCommon&lt;/div&gt;
      </para>
      <para>
        The LJC Code Backup program is not a generalized backup program but is
        designed specifically for backing up or promoting source code and other
        related text files. It is not designed for backup of binary files.
      </para>
      <para>
        When a developer is making changes to source code, it is challenging to
        keep track of which files were changed when it comes time to promote or
        backup the code. This is the task that the LJC Code Backup program is
        designed to automate.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </LJCBackupProgram>

  <!-- Methods -->
  <main>
    <summary>
      The program entry method.
    </summary>
  </main>
</members>