<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<!-- Copyright(c) Lester J. Clark and Contributors. -->
<!-- Licensed under the MIT License. -->
<!-- ProgramCreateFileChanges.xml -->
<items>
  <Program>
    <summary>
      The Create File Changes program.
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <para>-- Library Level Remarks</para>
      <para>
        The backup process runs in two parts. This is done to allow the user to
        review the proposed changes if desired before updating the target files.
      </para>
      <para>
        1. Run the LJCCreateFileChanges.exe program to create the "Changes"
        file.&lt;br /&gt;
        2. Run the LJCBackupChanges.exe program to perform the "Copy" and
        "Delete" messages in the "Change" file.
      </para>
      <para>
        The LJCCreateFileChanges.exe program's main functionality is provided in
        the file LJCCreateFileChangesLib.dll, class CreateFileChanges.
      </para>
      <para>
        The LJCCreateFileChanges.exe program creates a "Changes" file with the
        copy and delete commands for the updated files. The file commands
        contain the source filespec.
      </para>
      <para>
        The program takes four required parameters and one optional parameter.
      </para>
      <para>
        sourceRoot - The full path to the source files root folder. The files in
        this folder and all subfolders are available for backup.
      </para>
      <para>
        targetRoot - The full path to the target files root folder. The files in
        this folder and all subfolders are the target of the backup.&lt;br /&gt;
        Note: Only those folders that exist in the target will be updated.This
        is how the user controls what folders to backup. The target folders must
        be manually created to be included in the backup. The source folders and
        target folders must have matching names.&lt;br /&gt;
        This implicit approach prevents the user from having to specifically
        list the folders that are available for backup. The MissingFolders.txt
        file is written to show those folders that are not included.
      </para>
      <para>
        changesFileSpec - The full file specification for the "Changes" file.
      </para>
      <para>
        includeFilter - This is a list of file names that will are available for
        backup. The file names are separated with a vertial bar and can include
        wild cards and partial paths.
        Example: "*.cs|Doc\*.xml" This includes all files that end with the
        extension "cs" and all files that are in a "Doc" folder and end with the
        extension "xml".
      </para>
      <para>
        skipFiles - This optional parameter is a list of files that will not be
        changed.The file names are separated with a vertical bar and can include
        wild cards.&lt;br /&gt;
        Example: "Changes*.txt|?Build*.cmd" Files matching these names will not
        be updated or deleted.
      </para>
      <para>
        If the "Source" file is different from the "Target" file, then a "Copy"
        record is written to the "Changes" file.&lt;br /&gt;
        If a "Source" file is missing from the "Target", then a "Copy" record is
        written to the "Changes" file.&lt;br /&gt;
        If a file exists in the "Target" folder but does not exist in the
        "Source" folder, then a "Delete" record is written to the "Changes"
        file.
      </para>
    </remarks>
  </Program>  
</items>
